progressingemail.com 2007-10-07

# Progressing Markets Privacy Policy

Progressing Markets seeks to lead the internet marketing industry in customer-focused marketing efforts. We believe that in order to foster true relationships with our customers, we need to maintain the utmost respect for every customer's privacy. Below is an outline of our key policies we have in place in order to honor your privacy.

We seek to provide you with material that is relevant to you with chances to earn or win free prizes, get discounts or coupons, participate in surveys, or just get good deals for products and services.

## Regarding Your Email Address

We will never sell or rent your email address or the email addresses of your friends or contacts to anyone for any purpose.

## Non-Commercial Material

We will send you emails with notices about your account, or other transactional messages.

## Referrals of Friends

In order to refer your friends and contacts, you will be required to enter their email addresses and/or names. We will use this information to send emails to your friends and contacts asking them to participate in our program. The names and addresses you provide to us will be used to send a one-time email to those people. We will not send them future emails unless they confirm (or have already independently confirmed) their subscription to receive emails from Progressing Markets. All information you provide about your friends and contacts will be covered by this Privacy Policy. 

## Subscriptions to Promotional Materials

We will only send you marketing materials if you confirm your interest in receiving promotional materials. When you sign up to one of our websites, we send a one-time email asking you to confirm your interest in receiving promotional materials from us. If you do not confirm your interest, we will not send you any promotional materials.

The maximum number of emails messages which we will send you in any day is ALWAYS disclosed in our confirmation email. Our company policy is to not send more than 2 commercial messages per day to any customer.

## Unsubscribe to all Material

The fastest and easiest way to no longer get emails from us is to click the remove link provided at the bottom of each of our emails. This is a one-click remove process, so you will not have to enter any additional information in order to unsubscribe. It may take up to 48 hours for our systems to complete your request, but most people get removed instantly.

You can also reply to any email from us in order to get removed.

Finally, you can write to the postal address provided at the bottom of each of our emails and ask to stop receiving our emails. 

Our mailing address is:  
Progressing Markets, LLC, 106 E. 6th St, Ste 900, Austin, TX 78701.  
If you have any questions, you can always email: privacy@ProgressingMarkets.com  

## Unsubscribe to a specific friend's referral emails

At any time you can ask not to receive referral emails (which are delivered through our network) from a specific email account. 

Please email _Privacy@ProgressingMarkets.com_ , or write to the postal address above in order to request this removal. You must provide us with the email address(es) of the person or persons you do not want to receive referral emails from. 

It may take up to 48 hours from the time we receive your request for our systems to complete the removal.

## Regarding Your other Personal Information

As a reminder, we will never rent or sell your email address. However, we may allow trusted third parties to use your name, postal address and/or telephone number.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We will never ask for your social security number or your credit card number. If you are asked for either number, you are no longer on our website and are no longer interacting with Progressing Markets. You should review that website's policies to determine how they handle your personal information.

If you would like to unsubscribe from possible postal mailings, or phone calls, you can follow any of the unsubscribe instructions above. If your personal information or email address changes, you may correct or update it by emailing us at privacy@ProgressingMarkets.com and including both your old information and the necessary corrections in the email.

## Our Storage Policies

Our customers' information is stored on secure servers in secure facilities. We also maintain a reasonable number of backups stored in areas controlled by Progressing Markets. If you would like us to delete your information from our servers which interface with our customers, you can send us an email at privacy@ProgressingMarkets.com

## Website Tracking / Cookies

To obtain market research information, we may track what you do on our websites and emails, such as whether you open emails or click on emails. We may also track what you look at on our websites, how long you look at it, as well as what you click on. We do not track what you do on any other websites.

For your convenience we sometimes put cookies on your computer so that you can log in easily to our websites. We may also use these cookies to help us track what actions you take on our emails and websites.

## Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

We will share your email, name, postal address, phone number, birth date, and other personally identifiable information with third parties for the purpose of making it easier for you to register for third party websites. 

## Third Party Websites

Our website contains links to web sites of third party merchants, affiliated companies, co-branded partners and other parties. We are not responsible for, nor do we have any control over, the actions of these third parties, including their privacy practices and any content posted on their web sites. We do not examine or evaluate, and we do not warrant or claim responsibility in any way, for the products, services, offerings or business practices of any of these third party web sites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personal information. We adhere to industry recognized standards to secure any personal information in our possession, and to secure it from unauthorized access and tampering. However, as is true with all online actions, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions of personal information, or third party websites may misuse or abuse your personal information that they may collect from you.

IN THE EVENT OF A DISPUTE BETWEEN YOU AND A THIRD PARTY SITE, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, YOU RELEASE US, OUR SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, CO-BRAND PARTNERS OR OTHER THIRD PARTIES UNDER CONTRACT WITH US, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, AND LEGAL REPRESENTATIVES FROM AND AGAINST CLAIMS AND DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, KNOWN AND UNKNOWN, SUSPECTED AND UNSUSPECTED, DISCLOSED AND UNDISCLOSED, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH SUCH A DISPUTE.

If you are a California resident, by using our website, you explicitly waive the rights granted to you under California Civil Code 1542, which states: "A general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his favor at the time of executing the release, which, if known by him must have materially affected his settlement with the debtor."

## Third Party Communications About Our Site

It is possible that other third parties (including, but not limited, to your friends and contacts) may send information regarding our site. We are not responsible for, nor do we have any control over, the actions of these third parties. We do not examine or evaluate, and we do not warrant or claim responsibility in any way, for this information. If you encounter a problem, please contact us directly at privacy@ProgressingMarkets.com or the mailing address set forth above. We will try to assist you in solving the problem. 

## Legal Disclaimer

If required by law or if we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site, we will disclose your personal information.

## Business Transitions

In the event Progressing Markets, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by another company or a sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information may be among the assets sold or transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information and be given the time period in which you may ask to be unsubscribed.

## Changes to this Policy

If we ever change this policy or our e-mail practices, we will send you an e-mail notifying you of the change and, as always, you will have the option to be removed from our servers which interface with our customers.

WE WILL NOT CHANGE OUR PROMISE TO NEVER SELL OR RENT YOUR EMAIL.

Domain Addresses  
This Privacy Policy and Disclosure also applies to the following URL(s):

  * progressingprizes.com
  * progressingemail.com
  * progressingrewards.com
  * progressingdaily.com
  * instaprize.com
  * allamericansurvey(s).com
  * progressingaspconfirm.com
  * progressingaspoffer.com
  * progressingaspconfirm1.com
  * progressingaspoffer1.com
  * progressingaspconfirm2.com
  * progressingaspoffer2.com
  * progressingaspconfirm3.com
  * progressingaspoffer3.com
  * progressingaspconfirm4.com
  * progressingaspoffer4.com
  * progressingaspconfirm5.com
  * progressingaspoffer5.com
  * progressingaspconfirm6.com
  * progressingaspoffer6.com

Last Modified May 18, 2007
